Good evening, good morning or good afternoon!
晚上好，早上好或下午好！
Depending on when you're listening to my presentation.
取决于你什么时候听我的演讲。
First, let's talk about the topic which I've chosen.
首先，让我们谈谈我选择的主题。
It is somthing which has interested me a lot
这是一件让我很感兴趣的事情
For several years.
几年来。
It's about supporting people who want to create accessible digital content.
这是关于支持想要创建可访问的数字内容的人。
The scope of this project is "in an educational context"
该项目的范围是“在教育背景下”
So, who are we talking about? Who's the target group?
那么，我们在说谁？目标群体是谁？
This project, even if it's relevant for a lot of people
这个项目，即使它与很多人相关
The target group is teachers and other content creators
目标群体是教师和其他内容创作者
Who create digital content which is intended to be used in higher education.
谁创建旨在用于高等教育的数字内容。
So, what am I going to do in this project?
那么，我将在这个项目中做什么？
First, I am going to develop an interactive guide
首先，我将开发一个交互式指南
To help content creators create accessible digital content
帮助内容创建者创建可访问的数字内容
And it also has to be universally designed
它还必须是通用设计的
Why is this important?
为什么这很重要？
Aren't there enough resources out there already?
是不是已经没有足够的资源了？
Well, the problem is, there are so many resources out there
好吧，问题是，那里有这么多资源
You just don't know where to begin looking.
你只是不知道从哪里开始寻找。
Another factor that many people I have talked to are stressing is that
与我交谈过的许多人都强调的另一个因素是
It's the time! You don't have... Do you have the time?
是时候了！你没有……你有时间吗？
To spend hours, looking at different guides
花几个小时看不同的指南
to figure out exactly what do you have to do
弄清楚你必须做什么
to make this document, or this digital content accessible
使此文档或此数字内容可访问
this is a quote I actually heard from a teacher
这是我从老师那里听到的一句话
Something like "I am so stressed for time, just give me a list and show me how to do it!"
诸如“我的时间压力如此之大，请给我一份清单并告诉我该怎么做！”
So, how will I try to solve this problem?
那么，我将如何尝试解决这个问题呢？
My study uses a mixed methods approach
我的研究使用混合方法
We have one method for development
我们有一种开发方法
and another method for evaluation
和另一种评估方法
Now I will talk about development methodology
现在我来谈谈开发方法论
From Human Centered Design we have chosen
从以人为本的设计中，我们选择了
to use an iterative prototype development methodology
使用迭代原型开发方法
This is quite common in Human Centered Design.
这在以人为本的设计中很常见。
The idea is that
这个想法是
If you want to develop something for users
如果你想为用户开发一些东西
you have to involve them from the beginning
你必须从一开始就让他们参与进来
so how do you do this?
那么你是怎么做到的呢？
it's an iterative process
这是一个迭代的过程
you develop something small
你开发了一些小东西
and you get some users to test it
你让一些用户来测试它
and the users in this case are from the target group
并且这种情况下的用户来自目标群体
which are university teachers and other staff
他们是大学教师和其他工作人员
so we get user feedback
所以我们得到用户反馈
from the first iteration of the prototype
从原型的第一次迭代
based on this feedback
基于此反馈
we decide on how to improve the prototype
我们决定如何改进原型
for the next generation
为下一代
so the iterative process continues for several generations
所以迭代过程持续了几代
or we call it "iterations"
或者我们称之为“迭代”
This is also part of the development methodology
这也是开发方法的一部分
There's something called
有一种东西叫
low fidelity vs high fidelity prototypes
低保真与高保真原型
low fidelity, we can also call it paper prototyping
低保真度，我们也可以称之为纸质原型
which means we can sketch out some ideas on paper
这意味着我们可以在纸上勾勒出一些想法
all we need is paper, pen, maybe scissors
我们只需要纸、笔，也许还有剪刀
and we can start brainstorming ideas
我们可以开始集思广益
try to figure out what is this thing we're making
试着弄清楚我们在做什么
what's it going to be like
会是什么样子
the advantage to using paper prototyping
使用纸质原型的优势
or low fidelity prototyping
或低保真原型
is that you can generate a lot of ideas quite quickly
是你可以很快产生很多想法
and not a lot of time is invested
而且投入的时间不多
so it's easy to scrap some bad ideas and try out some new ideas
所以很容易报废
when we reach a stage that the design has stabilized a little bit
当我们达到设计稍微稳定的阶段时
then we can move on to high fidelity prototyping
然后我们可以继续进行高保真原型制作
these are more time consuming
这些更耗时
and they can be interactive and quite close to the final product or prototype
它们可以是交互式的，并且非常接近最终产品或原型
in this case I'm developing an interactive guide in the form of a webpage
在这种情况下，我正在开发一个网页形式的交互式指南
so, in the low fidelity stage, which I actually did before involving users
所以，在低保真阶段，我在涉及用户之前实际上是这样做的
I used paper and pen
我用纸和笔
and then with user feedback I was working in the high fidelity prototyping stage
然后根据用户反馈，我在高保真原型设计阶段工作
after developing the final prototype...
在开发出最终原型之后...
you know, you can go on forever to improve a prototype
你知道，你可以永远继续改进原型
but at some time, at some point, we just have to stop and evaluate it
但在某些时候，在某些时候，我们只需要停下来评估它
so how do we evaluate this interactive guide?
那么我们如何评价这个互动指南呢？
well, we choose some participants
好吧，我们选择一些参与者
and either, we can ask them to present some documents they have made before
或者，我们可以要求他们出示他们之前制作的一些文件
or I will do a heuristic review of these documents
或者我将对这些文件进行启发式审查
this means that I will have a checklist of different things I'm looking for
这意味着我将有一份我正在寻找的不同事物的清单
different accessibility mistakes I will be looking for in these documents
我将在这些文档中寻找不同的可访问性错误
and then the participant can have access to this guide and try to create some new documents
然后参与者可以访问本指南并尝试创建一些新文档
and I can also do a heuristic review of the documents they are making when they have access to this guide
当他们可以访问本指南时，我还可以对他们正在制作的文档进行启发式审查
then I can compare before and after (having access to the interactive guide)
然后我可以比较之前和之后（可以访问交互式指南）
what kind of accessibility mistakes have been made
犯了什么样的可访问性错误
we also collect data qualitatively
我们还定性地收集数据
by user observation which is similar to user testing
通过类似于用户测试的用户观察
when we have a participant who is creating some digital content
当我们有一个参与者正在创建一些数字内容时
while using the interactive guide
在使用交互式指南时
which is supposed to help them create accessible content
这应该可以帮助他们创建可访问的内容
then I will just be observing and making notes
那我就只是观察和做笔记
then after, we will have the users or participants fill out something called
然后，我们会让用户或参与者填写一些名为
the system usability scale, which is a lickert scale
系统可用性量表，这是一个利克特量表
It will ask different questions about how usable this guide is
它将就本指南的可用性提出不同的问题
and finally, we will interview the participants using semi structured interviews
最后，我们将使用半结构化访谈方式采访参与者
so, what are the preliminary results
那么，初步结果是什么
well some of the results are the feedback I have already received
好吧，有些结果是我已经收到的反馈
some of the types of feedback received
收到的一些反馈类型
is about the structure of the guide, also naming of things, language and grammar
是关于指南的结构，还有事物的命名、语言和语法
several users commented that they were looking forward to
几位用户评论说他们很期待
specific instructions on different software they would be using
他们将使用的不同软件的具体说明
also the guide has some filtering which needs to be fixed
该指南也有一些过滤需要修复
there are different kinds of parameters that will taylor the guide to the user's needs
有不同种类的参数可以根据用户的需求定制指南
so if you're working with video, you will have an interactive guide
因此，如果您正在使用视频，您将获得一个交互式指南
which will tell you about how to make an accessible video
它将告诉您如何制作可访问的视频
if your'e working with a document, say in Word
如果您正在处理文档，请在 Word 中说
then you will have a taylored guide which will give you
然后你会有一个定制的指南，它会给你
the tips you need when working with documents in Word
在 Word 中处理文档时需要的提示
and also what kind of content you have there
还有你那里有什么样的内容
if you have images, then you can get image specific feedback
如果您有图像，那么您可以获得图像特定的反馈
so another preliminary result is the result of
所以另一个初步结果是
implementing the feedback from round 1 actually
实际执行第一轮的反馈
This is the beginning, the top of the webpage
这是开始，网页顶部
before considering the second round of feedback
在考虑第二轮反馈之前
So I think that will be all for this presentation
所以我认为这就是本次演讲的全部内容
I will be seeing you later!
我以后会见到你的！